var hpQuiz = [{
  "question": "What was the spell Snape used on the whomping willow?",
  "options": ["Impedimenta", "Fidelius", "Immobulus", "Reducio"],
  "answer": 2,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "What is kissing called?",
  "options": ["Frenching", "Snogging", "Slugging", "Snubbing"],
  "answer": 1,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "What is the name of Draco Malfoy's son?",
  "options": ["Scorpius", "Lucius", "Diego", "Severus", "Dane"],
  "answer": 0,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "What creature does Dumbledore have as a pet?",
  "options": ["Efreet", "Fey", "Troll", "Phoenix", "Basilisk"],
  "answer": 3,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "What is Voldemort's final horcrux?",
  "options": ["A mirror", "A snake", "A brooch", "Harry Potter"],
  "answer": 1,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "Who takes over as headmaster of Hogwarts after Dumbledore's death?",
  "options": ["Narcissa Black", "Professor Trelawny", "Delores Umbridge", "Professor Snape"],
  "answer": 3,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "Who killed Deatheater Antonin Dolohov during the Battle of Hogwarts?",
  "options": ["Professor Flitwick", "Ron Weasley", "Falling Debris", "Hermione Granger"],
  "answer": 0,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "Who was the old Care of Magical Creatures teacher?",
  "options": ["Professer Kettleburn", "Professor Hagrid", "Professor Lupin", "Professor Grubbly-Plank"],
  "answer": 0,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "How much does a twelve-week course of Apparition lessons cost?",
  "options": ["17 Galleons", "12 Galleons", "3 Galleons", "Nothing - It's Free"],
  "answer": 1,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "How much gold do the Weasleys win in the annual Daily Prophet Grand Prize Galleon Draw?",
  "options": ["800 Galleons", "7k Galleons", "700 Galleons", "700 Sickles"],
  "answer": 2,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "Where do Harry's aunt and uncle live?",
  "options": ["Little Hangleton", "Hogsmeade", "Little Whinging", "Godric's Hollow"],
  "answer": 2,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "How many times do Fred and George's fireworks multiply by if you try to vanish them?",
  "options": ["25", "20", "10", "15"],
  "answer": 2,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "How many times was Nearly Headless Nick hit in the neck with a blunt axe?",
  "options": ["47", "45", "20", "25"],
  "answer": 1,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "What do Ron and Hermione use to destroy Helga Hufflepuff's cup?",
  "options": ["A basilisk Fang", "Fiendfyre", "Sword of Gryffindor", "Patronum Charm"],
  "answer": 0,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "What is Dumbledore's full name?",
  "options": ["Albus Percival Brian Wulfric Dumbledore", "Albus Wulfric Brian Percival Dumbledore", "Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore"],
  "answer": 2,
  "isAnswered": false 
},

{ 
  "question": "What does O.W.L. stand for?",
  "options": ["Offical Wizarding License", "Organised Wizard Learning", "Ordinary Wizarding Level", "Outstanding Wizard Lesson"],
  "answer": 2,
  "isAnswered": false 
}]
